本集结束之后 敬请继续关注
堡垒
解密档案
《堡垒》前情提要
你是要把我们母女俩丢在这里 然后跟他走吗
You're just gonna leave us here and go with him?
是时候了
It's time.
只要我们夺回那个箱子
We get this case back,
我就能确保你和亨德里克斯的安全 我只在乎这个
I get to keep you and Hendrix safe. That's all I care about.
我们被攻破了 箱子被偷了
We got breeched and the case was stolen.
是梅森凯恩干的
It was Mason Kane.
把箱子给我带来 把凯恩也带来
Bring me the case. And Kane.
开稳一点
Steady.
我很欣慰你活了下来
I'm so glad you pulled through.
我尤为擅长让堡垒的特工叛变
I'm exceptionally skilled at getting Citadel agents to turn.
你确实有过一个搭档
You did have a partner.
她叫纳迪亚辛赫
Her name was Nadia Sinh.
强强联手 你俩更是炙手可热
Together, you were hot stuff.
我觉得她死了
I think she's dead.
后盾开启中
Backstop commencing.
唯一能帮到我的人是一个堡垒间谍 但他们失去了记忆
The only person who can help me is a Citadel spy.
实在是抱歉
But they've lost their memories.
你是纳迪亚
- You're Nadia.
-并不是 -你跟我一样也是间谍
- No. - You were a spy like me.
-这是... -是你
That's... You.
把那个小药瓶注射进你的脖子里
That vial there, you inject it into your neck.
这样你的记忆就恢复了
It'll bring back your memories.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen...
纳迪亚辛赫
Nadia Sinh.
我以为梅森死了
I thought Mason was dead.
你记得了
You remember.
我什么都记得
I remember everything.
? Try not to get worried ?
? Try not to turn on to ?
? Problems that upset you ?
? Don't you know everything's all right ?
? Yes, everything's fine ?
? And we want you to sleep well tonight ?
? Let the world turn without you tonight ?
? If we try, we'll get by ?
? So forget all about us tonight ?
? Tonight, yes, everything's all right ?
? Sleep and I shall soothe you ?
? Calm you and anoint you ?
? Myrrh for your hot forehead...
准备好尝第二道菜了吗
Ready for seconds?
? Yes, everything's fine ?
? Close your eyes, close your eyes...
堡垒
第一季第三集
本WEB版外挂字幕由  风吹来的那片云  双语合并
西班牙 卡塞雷斯
戴维克在X箱子里放了追踪器
Davik put a tracker in the X Case.
我已将其禁用
I disabled it.
他找不到我们这里来
He won't find us here.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
是堡垒的安全屋
Citadel safe house.
以前我们有成百个这种安全屋
We used to have hundreds of them.
我们以前来过这里吗
You and I been here before?
来过一两次
Once or twice.
咱俩以前关系好吗
Were we close?
不算好吧
Not particularly.
我能信任你吗
Can I trust you?
这个问题你已经不是第一次问我了
Not the first time you've asked me that.
来吧
Come on.
咬着这个
Bite this.
会很疼的
This will hurt.
我会温柔一点
- I'll be gentle.
-我感觉你根本不会温柔 -咬住
- I got a feeling you don't know how to be. - Bite.
取出来了
Got it.
疼死了
Damn it.
跟我聊聊她吧
So, tell me about her.
谁
Who?
你妻子
- Your wife.
艾比
Abby.
结婚多久了
- How long?
八年
- Eight years.
看来你是一分钟都没耽误啊
Wow. You didn't waste any time.
我们生了个姑娘 叫亨德里克斯
We have a daughter, Hendrix.
你没事吧
You okay?
没事
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
跟我聊聊他吧
Tell me about him.
谁
Who?
梅森 他是什么样的人
Mason. Who was he?
没办法跟你说 我跟他关系没那么近
Couldn't tell you. We weren't that close.
纯粹是工作关系 从来没有私人交情
It was all about the job, never got personal.
从来没有
Never?
因为我什么都不记得了
'Cause I couldn't remember anything.
名字 家庭 出生地 全都不记得了
Not my name, my family, where I was from. I couldn't remember anything...
我只记得你
except you.
我最擅长给别人留下深刻的印象
I've been known to leave an impression.
咱俩以前是一对儿吗
Were we together?
从我记得的来看 感觉咱俩以前是一对儿
'Cause from what I remember it felt like we were.
你这个健忘症患者也好意思说
Says an amnesiac.
到底是吗
Were we?
我们在一起的时间很短暂 算不了什么
It was brief. It was nothing.
终成眷属
Lightning in a bottle?
说是"昙花一现"还差不多
Flash... in a pan.
犹他州 十年前
堡垒陷落之前
堡垒 美国总部
我们不是要开情况通报会吗
We having a briefing or what?
-他们迟到五分钟了 -"迟到五分钟"
They're running five behind. "Running five behind"?
嘿
Hey.
怎么了
What?
-快说啊 兄弟 -不行
- Come on, man. - No.
你知道格雷斯讨厌我剧透她要说的话
You know how Grace hates it when I steal her thunder.
-怂包 -好吧
- Chickenshit. - All right.
但等她进来的时候 你一定要假装是第一次听到
But you have to pretend like you're hearing it for the first time when she comes in.
-我不一直是这样做的吗  -从来都不是
- Don't I always? - Almost never.
有话快说
Spit it out.
哈桑创造出了一种新病毒
Hasan has created a new virus.
未来几天内 他的团伙将在美国释放这种病毒
His syndicate's gonna release it in the U.S. within days.
这是一种人工改造的埃博拉病毒 它将会引发瘟疫
It's a manipulated strain of Ebola, and it'll cause a plague
这将是自中世纪黑暗时代以来 世人从未见过的场面
the likes of which the world hasn't seen since the Dark Ages.
好了 我们的情报显示 哈桑的团伙创造出了一种新病毒...
All right, we have intel that Hasan's syndicate has created a...
并计划未来几天内 在美国释放这种新病毒
A new virus he plans to release in the U.S. within days.
这是一种埃博拉病毒 将会引发瘟疫
A manipulated strain of Ebola, which would cause a plague
会造成自中世纪黑暗时代以来 世人从未见过的场面
the likes of which the world hasn't seen since the Dark Ages.
都是伯纳德告诉我的 我们比你们早五分钟
Bernard caught me up. We were running five ahead.
伯纳德 认真的吗
Seriously, Bernard?
我就是预先通报了一下 仅此而已
It was just a pre-briefing, that's all, nothing.
你真是个混蛋
Such a dick.
情报证实 该病毒被储存在
Our intelligence confirms the virus is being stored in
厄尔布尔士山脉的一个研究机构中
an advanced research facility in the Alborz Mountains.
厄尔布尔士山脉 为什么就不能是 阿卡普尔科 伯利兹或伊比萨岛呢
Alborz Mountains. Why is it never Acapulco? Or Belize, or Ibiza?
她还没说上几句话呢
Come on. She's barely two seconds in
你就像斯塔特勒 和沃尔多夫一样质问她
and you're heckling her like Statler and Waldorf.
你们知道吧  就是《大青蛙布偶秀》里那俩老布偶
You know, the Muppets? The two old Muppets?
-我觉得你才是那个老布偶 -好吧
Yeah, I think you're the old Muppet, Bernard. - Okay.
总结一下 有个所向披靡的敌人 在坚不可摧的要塞里
- So, to recap, an impossible foe has an unthinkable virus
藏了个超乎想象的病毒 而我的任务是把它偷来
in an impenetrable fortress, and I'm gonna steal it.
我们新来的一级行动员将会到场 他们是卧底
Our newest Tier-One will be on-site. They've been working
把病毒放在了便于我们取回的位置
as a mole with Hasan and planted the virus for easy retrieval.
难点不在于怎么进去 而在于怎么出来
The hard part isn't getting in, it's getting out.
要塞有重兵把守 此外还有监控和导弹系统
There are heavily armed guards, surveillance and missile systems.
但你走运了 因为你还会有援军
Lucky for you, you'll have some help.
我们新来的特工将会协助你
Our newest agent will assist you.
让菜鸟协助我
A rookie's gonna assist me?
-我怎么认出他们  -到时候自然就知道了
- How will I know them? - Oh, you'll know.
伊朗 厄尔布尔士山脉 24小时后
耶
Yes!
拿到了高分
Got the high score.
阿尔法五分钟后撤离
Alpha is five minutes to exit.
-公爵 报告情况 -空中支援已入境
- Duke, status report? - Air support inbound.
收到
Copy.
梅森 你比计划的时间提前了
Mason, you're ahead of schedule.
货物得手了  我拿到了病毒 东出口
Package in hand! I have the virus! East exit.
珀加索斯 他在东出口
Pegasus, he's at the east exit.
梅森 距离三公里 即将发起进攻 武器准备就绪
Mason, I'm three klicks out. 'Bout to roll in. Weapons hot.
你六点钟方向有两个伞兵
Two paratroopers on your six.
敌人的全地形车正在从山的南侧驶来
Enemy ATVs coming up the south side of the mountain.
发现导弹正在飞向你的位置
I'm picking up missiles, incoming on your position.
快点 阿尔法
Got to hustle, Alpha.
特工离线
Agent off-line.
正在尝试重新连接
Attempting to reconnect.
阿尔法 快起来啊
Alpha.
通讯已恢复
Comms reconnected.
敌人的全地形车正在快速逼近 你被包围了
Enemy ATVs fast approaching. They've got you surrounded.
那可未必
- Not quite.
不要 你他妈要干吗
- Mason, no, no, no! What the hell are you doing?
搭个车
Catching a ride!
动作快点 梅森 敌人从空中来了
Look alive, Mason. We got hostiles in the air.
启动滑雪靴
Activate ski-boots.
珀加索斯 去新撤离点 我们山脚下见
Pegasus, new extraction point. Meet me at the bottom of the mountain.
收到 还有两公里
Copy that. Two ticks out.
更刺激的来了 地面上发现两辆车
More excitement for you, Alpha. I'm seeing two vehicles on the ground.
圣诞快乐 阿尔法
Merry Christmas, Alpha.
雪量快用光了
Heads up, the snow line is ending.
重复 你的雪量快耗尽了
I repeat, you are running out of snow.
梅森 有五辆全地形车正在上山
Mason, five ATVs are heading up the mountain.
你有三根肋骨骨折 以及内出血
Alpha, you've got three broken ribs and internal bleeding.
我会坚持完成任务的
I'm pushing through it.
(波斯语) 住手
Stop!
就是她 她就是我们的新特工
That's her. That's our new agent.
我没子弹了
I'm out!
左肺充血
That left lung is filling up with blood,
氧气含量不足 而且你脑震荡了
oxygen levels running low. And you're also concussed.
就是这些情况
So, there's that.
给我枪
Gun!
他内出血了 血压在下降
He's hemostatic. Blood pressure's dropping.
前往向南三公里位于空地上的撤离点
Gemini, head to the extraction point three klicks south, in the clearing.
收到 正在前往 我们走
Copy. En route. Come on.
坚持住
Hang on.
你...
You...
保持清醒 好吗
Stay with me, okay?
好吗
Yeah?
我不方便
I'm busy.
抱歉 我不想打扰你 但我就是觉得应该自我介绍一下
Sorry, I don't want to disturb you, I just thought I'd introduce myself.
纳迪亚辛赫
Nadia Sinh.
梅森凯恩
Mason Kane.
不客气 梅森凯恩
You're welcome, Mason Kane.
你说什么
Excuse me?
你差点就把整个任务搅黄了
Well, you almost blew the entire mission.
差点就让美国的一半人口感染病毒了
Half of the U.S. would be infected by now.
-当时的局面尽在我掌控之中 -是吗
- I had it covered. - Did you, though?
小菜鸟 我是那种人
That's the thing about me, Rookie.
当你觉得我已经没有胜算的时候 我就会扭转乾坤
Just when you think I'm down and out, I'll turn it around.
好吧
Right, right, right.
对了 有句话我们必须说清楚
Also, just so we're very fucking clear,
我不是菜鸟
not a rookie.
你是哪来的 军情六处
Where'd you come from? MI6?
-印度情报局  -我可是土生土长的
- IB? - I'm homegrown.
我母亲是堡垒的特工 我五年前加入了堡垒
My mother was Citadel, I joined five years ago.
来自精英小队
Came up through Bravo Team.
精英小队 不错 了不起
Bravo Team. That's cute. That's adorable.
你知道最了不起的是什么吗
You know what's adorable?
你的上级求着我加入一级行动员 好让我救你狗命
Is your director begging me to join Tier-One just in time to save your ass.
这就是我魅力的一部分
That... is part of my charm.
有个当间谍的妈 从小到大肯定很不容易吧
Must've been hard growing up with a spy for a mother.
连个妈都没有 从小到大肯定很不容易吧
Must've been hard growing up with no mother at all.
抱歉
Sorry.
你看了我的资料
You read my file.
没想到你还是我的粉丝呢
Didn't pin you for a fan.
我一般不这么做 但我可以给你签名
You know, I don't usually do this, but I could sign an autograph.
跟你自拍
Take a selfie?
小心我干你
Fuck you.
那也尽在我掌控之中
I would've had it covered.
巴黎 两周后
我能信任你吗
Can I trust you?
当然了
Of course.
我能信任你吗
Can I trust you?
永远可以信任我
Always.
堡垒安全屋 十年后
私人模式已启动
Private mode initiated.
登录中...
发送安全信息
天气怎么样
基本上是晴天
真的是你吗
是的
货物怎么样了
在等你
瓦伦西亚可能暴露了
准备好应急措施 我很快就到
见到你我真开心 伯纳德
Nice to see you, Bernard.
见到你是真他妈糟糕 黛丽娅
It's horrifically fucking terrible to see you, Dahlia.
糟糕透顶
Couldn't be worse.
我想你看到我坐在桌子的这一头 很震惊吧
I imagine it's a shock to see me at this end of the table.
这倒是 我原以为你会在吸血
Yeah. I thought you might be at a blood-feed,
或者搞动物献祭 或者在忙你每周的女巫集会呢
or an animal sacrifice or your weekly coven meeting.
虽然多年前我们曾一起在联合国工作
Even when we were together all those years ago at the U.N.,
但你总是有那种 不可描述的反社会的特质
you always had that sociopathic je ne sais quois about you.
给他看看
Show him.
在我们拿到X箱子之前 只能用手头掌握的一些堡垒技术了
Until we get the X Case, we'll have to make do with what we've got.
我们尽全力抢救了 还没来得及被你的间谍破坏的
We made sure to salvage every piece of Citadel tech
每一项堡垒的技术
that wasn't sabotaged by your spies.
这其中最好用的 当属堡垒人工智能系统
Among the delights was a Citadel A.I. system
它能追踪世界各地的铀含量
that tracked uranium levels throughout the world.
还能随时追踪 全世界所有核武器的下落
The whereabouts, at any time, of all nuclear weapons.
唯一的问题是 我们无法进入系统 我们已经试了很多年
Only, we can't access the system. We've tried for years.
但仿佛天降恩赐一般 你作为系统的创始人
But here before me, like a gift from God,
就坐在我的面前
sits the man who created it.
所以 伯纳德
So, Bernard,
你要告诉我 进入系统所需要的19位数的密码
you need to tell me the 19-character password to access the system.
好吧
Okay. Okay.
密码是...
The password is...
"你
"Why...
"为什么
...don't...you...
"不趁早滚蛋呢 "
...fuck off."
不对 这只有18个字符
Oh, no, wait, that's only 18.
抱歉 要19个字符
I'm sorry, it's 19.
还有个感叹号 抱歉
There's an exclamation mark. Forgive me.
"你为什么不趁早滚蛋呢 感叹号"
"Why don't you fuck off, exclamation mark."
试试
Go ahead.
你真觉得为了阻止你 我做不到置生死于度外吗
Do you really think that I wouldn't give my life to stop you?
也许你能做到吧 但你老婆和女儿的命呢
Maybe, but what about the lives of your wife and daughter?
-她们在怀俄明州 对吧  -我完全不知道你在说什么
They're in Wyoming, right? I have no idea what you're talking about.
她们跟梅森凯恩的妻子和女儿在一起
With Mason Kane's wife and daughter,
不是吗
no?
这把刀是我妈给我的第一把
That knife is the first one my mom gave me.
如果按下这个按钮
If you push the thumb button,
刀片就会弹出来
blade just flicks out.
太帅了
Cool.
你想要的话就给你了
You can have it if you want.
我给你演示一下怎么用
I'll show you how to use it.
嘿
Hey.
你跟你老公是怎么认识的
So, how did you and your husband meet?
大概九年前 我出了一场严重的车祸
Uh, well, I was, um... I was in a bad car accident about nine years ago.
太不幸了
That's awful.
我不记得了 创伤性脑损伤
I don't remember it. Traumatic brain injury.
总之 我们家附近有一家很棒的医院
Anyway, um, there was a great hospital nearby.
我在那里开始接受记忆疗法 当时凯尔也在...
And I started memory therapy there. And, um, Kyle was just...
他也参加了同样的项目
He was in the same program.
我俩就这样认识了
That's how we met.
这故事真精彩
Quite a story.
她们不在怀俄明州 我都不知道她们在哪里
They're not in Wyoming. I don't even know where they are.
别装了 我们到处都有眼线
Oh, come on, Bernard, we have eyes everywhere.
我们能访问所有安防探头和卫星
Access to every security camera, every satellite on the grid.
你开车去了我们的纽约总部 所以我们顺着你的轨迹倒查
You drove your truck to our New York headquarters, so we worked backwards, used every camera
用每个探头拼凑出了你去时的路线
at our disposal to piece your journey back to where you came from.
追溯到夏延郊外就查不到你的车了 所以 找到你妻子乔
We lost image of your truck just outside Cheyenne. So it's only a matter of time
以及你女儿瓦尔 只是时间早晚的问题
before we find your wife Joe and your daughter Val.
顺便一提 她是我前妻
She's my ex-wife, by the way.
而且我早告诉过你了...
And I told you already.
趁早滚蛋
Fuck off.
一个世纪以来 你们都认为自己是在创造新秩序
For a century, you lot thought you were creating a new order.
但间谍不可能是圣人
But spies cannot be saints.
你们的行为准则 非但没能让你们变得更好
And your code isn't one that bettered you, but blinded you...
反而让你们 对堡垒带来的恐怖熟视无睹
to the horrors Citadel imparted.
你错了
You're wrong.
是吗
Am I?
你的同事以前也是这样的想法
Your colleague thought the same.
但去年我们抓到他之后 就给他看了真相
But after we caught him last year, we pulled the wool from over his eyes.
卡特斯宾塞
Carter Spence.
-卡特  -没错 他最开始
- Carter? - Yes. He was quite uncooperative...
极为不配合
to begin with.
拼了命硬撑着
Held out for as long as he could.
-他在哪  -卡沃医生
- Where is he? - Dr. Carvo?
你把卡特怎么样了
What did you do to Carter?
你这么爱说话的人 怎么变得这么安静啊 伯纳德
For a man who loves to talk, you've gone awfully quiet, Bernard.
好吧...
Well...
我在学着多一些倾听
I'm learning to listen more.
我们还有一种方法
There is another way we could do this.
我们可以
We could...
直接
...cut right
切入你的脑干
into your brain stem.
提取你的记忆
Excavate your memories.
这是安德斯希尔杰发明的一个 很好用的小装置
It's a handy little device Anders Silje created.
先生们
Gentlemen.
你准备好玩玩新玩具了吗
You ready to play with your new toy?
是的 夫人
Yes, ma'am.
别搞砸了
Don't fuck it up.
你是哪一位来着
Which one are you, again?
玛丽凯特还是阿什莉
Mary-Kate or Ashley?
梅森凯恩是你朋友 对吧
Mason Kane is a friend of yours, right?
我可不会把他算作朋友
I wouldn't say he's a friend. I mean,
他可能会说我俩是朋友
he'd probably say we're friends.
他可能会说我是他最好的朋友
Probably he'd say I'm his best friend, but...
但他的朋友并不多 很可悲
he doesn't have many friends. It's very sad.
我以前在工作中有很多朋友
I had a lot of friends at work.
卡尔P 安德里亚
Carl P. and Andrea.
还有卡尔H
And Carl H.
还有吉姆
And Jim.
但他们都已经不在了
But they're not around anymore.
奥立克先生 我研究过你的所有杰作
I've studied all your work, Mr. Orlick.
不得不说 我是你的忠实粉丝
And I have to admit that I'm a big fan.
人们常说:"千万别见自己的偶像"
They say never meet your heroes,
但我很欣慰见到了你 知道为什么吗
but I'm so glad I am. You know why?
因为对凯恩的朋友
'Cause it gives me great pleasure
进行这样的操作
to do this...
能给我带来极大的快感
...to a friend of Kane's.
无论用什么方式 我都会拿到我想要的
Now I'm going to get what I want no matter what.
我们就盼着 我别破坏掉伯纳德奥立克的
Let's just hope we don't destroy the brilliant mind
聪明才智吧
of Bernard Orlick.
布瑞尔还活着
Brielle is still alive.
什么 你刚才说什么
- What... - What did you just say?
我说:"布瑞尔还活着"
I said, Brielle is still alive.
你爱的女人是叫布瑞尔吧 不是吗
The woman you loved. That's her name, isn't it? Brielle?
堡垒骗了你
Citadel lied to you.
如果你这又是在耍花样
If this is another trick,
我就把你大卸八块
I'm gonna tear you apart.
听明白了吗
You understand?
我发誓
I swear.
那你最好证明给我看
Well, you better prove it then.
把我的手机拿来
Bring me my phone...
我给你看
and I'll show you.
你俩还好吗
How you two doing?
你知道的...
Oh, you know.
除了我不让亨德里克斯在地堡里 刷短视频 导致她情绪有点崩溃之外
Other than Hendrix having a meltdown because I won't let her TikTok from the bunker...
我们挺好的
...we're fine.
那个堡垒的间谍 我找到她了
Well, I found her... the, uh, Citadel spy.
她什么都记得
She remembers everything.
是女的
She?
是的
Yeah.
她叫纳迪亚
Her name's Nadia.
那是好事啊
I mean, that's-that's great.
她是怎么说梅森的 她还知道什么
What-what did she say about Mason? What else did she know?
她知道的并不多
Not a lot.
你们俩以前认识吗
Did you two not know each other?
好像不太认识
I don't think well.
我们会把事情搞定 然后我就回你身边
We're gonna figure this out and then I'm coming back to you, okay?
好的
Yeah.
搞定之后就回来
Figure it out and come back.
我会的
I will.
尽可能多打电话联系我们
Call as much as you can.
我会的
I will.
我爱你 凯尔
I love you, Kyle.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
你开车去巴拉哈斯机场吧
Drive yourself to Barajas airport.
坐飞机回美国 这里有一些现金
Catch a plane back to the States. Here's some cash.
我要留下来陪你
I'm staying with you.
他们看到我们了 知道我们还活着 他们杀了伯纳德
They saw us. They know we're alive. They killed Bernard.
他们会来追杀我们
They're gonna come after us with everything they've got.
你应该回去保护好家人
You need to go home and protect your family.
如果我真回去了 他们会找到我
If I go home, they're gonna find me.
只有阻止他们 我才能保护家人
Stopping them, that's how I protect my family.
-你对我来说毫无用处 -伯纳德可不是这么认为的
- You're of no use to me. - Bernard didn't think so.
伯纳德很蠢 而你就是个累赘
Bernard was a fool. And you're a liability.
教教我
Teach me.
-教什么  -教我当梅森凯恩
- What? - To be Mason Kane.
-你在说什么  -训练我
- What are you talking about? - Train me.
-我会边学边干 -你不是他
- I'll learn on the go. - You're not him.
-我可以是他 -你不会想变成他
- I can be. - You don't want to be him.
没有别人了 只剩下咱俩了
Well, there's no one else. It's just you and me.
一片红色的海洋里 只有两个闪烁的白点
Two flashing white lights in a sea of red.
什么红色的海洋
What sea of red?
闪烁的灯是求救信号 搜索信件
Flashing lights are an SOS. "Search Missives."
这些都是求救的信息
These are all messages. Calls for help.
我是特工卡特斯宾塞
This is Agent Carter Spence,
我在北京
I'm in Beijing.
如果还有其他幸存的堡垒特工
If there are any other surviving Citadel agents,
可以通过安全服务器联系我
you can contact me on the secure server,
D-G-6-4-6-2-1
Delta Gamma 64621.
卡特
Carter...
我是特工卡特斯宾塞
This is Agent Carter Spence.
我刚到墨西哥城
I just got to Mexico City.
求你们了 如果还有谁...
Please, if there is anyone else out there...
这也就是四个月前的信息
This was only four months ago.
我是特工卡特斯宾塞
This is... Agent Carter Spence.
我在菲斯
I'm in Fez.
曼提柯尔正在接近我的位置
Manticore's closing in on my location.
求你们了 如果有谁在看这个信息 这可能是我最后一次通讯
Please, if you are watching this, this might be my last transmission.
妈的
Shit.
我知道他在哪
I know where he is.
在这里
Here.
距菲斯几公里之外
He's a few miles outside of Fez.
这是个暗点
It's a black site.
你怎么知道的
How do you know?
我在青年党当卧底的时候 曾在那里受了两周的酷刑
'Cause I was tortured there for two weeks when I was undercover with al-Shahaab.
这个暗点的老大是一个叫 鲍德温巴斯托的葡萄牙黑帮老大
This black site's run by a Portuguese crime boss named Balduino Basto.
我敢肯定这个暗点为曼提柯尔所用了
I bet Manticore's using it.
通过折磨卡特 以获取X箱子的位置
Torturing Carter to get the location of the X Case.
我得把他救出来
I got to get him out.
-怎么救  -鲍德温
- How? - Balduino.
我只需要离他足够近 就能黑进他的手机 窃取访问代码
I just have to get close enough to hack his phone to steal his access codes.
问题是 他对我没有好意
Problem is he's not a fan of yours truly.
为什么
And why is that?
-我可能杀了他的哥哥 -"可能杀了"
I might have killed his brother. Might have?
我不能跟鲍德温见面
I can't get a sit-down with Balduino.
但他跟凯恩关系友好
But him and Kane, they were tight.
所以你的意思是...
So what you're saying is...
你准备好当梅森凯恩了吗
Are you ready to be Mason Kane?
摩洛哥
记住我跟你说的 你要以诚恳的态度接近鲍德温
Remember what I told you. Approach Balduino with your palms up.
表明你不是个威胁 这样一来你应该就安全了
Establish you're not a threat and you should be straight.
我餐厅里居然来了个死人
There's a dead man in my restaurant.
好久不见啊
It's been a long time.
打火机里有个接收器
There's a transmitter in that lighter.
在我从他手机里下载数据时 你尽可能把打火机放近一点
Keep it as close as possible while I download the data from his phone.
我以为八年前他们把你杀了
I thought they killed you eight years ago.
别坐立不安了
Stop fidgeting.
你是梅森凯恩 镇定点
You're Mason Kane. Own it.
然而这么久了 你却连一根头发丝儿都没长出来
And yet in all this time you haven't bothered to grow one single hair.
你这次来想干什么
So, what do you want?
你假意求他帮大忙 他肯定会很嘚瑟
Needs to be a big ask. It'll stroke his ego.
我需要你帮忙 把我弄进武装部队总司令的办公室
I need your help to get into the office of the Chief of the Armed Forces.
那是鲍德温的孩子
That's Baldy's kid.
他说让你去死
He just told you to go fuck yourself.
就没有个儿童球池 能让你家孩子去玩吗
Isn't there a ball pit somewhere your kid can go play in?
武装部队总司令
The Chief of Armed Forces?
你还不如直接让我
You might as well have asked me how to get
把你送到剑桥公爵夫人的两腿之间呢
between the legs of the Duchess of Cambridge.
我会帮你摆脱曼提柯尔
I'll get Manticore's heel off your neck.
现在江湖上是曼提柯尔一家独大
Manticore is the only game in town now.
我敢说 我要把你交给他们 肯定能大赚一笔
And I bet I could make a fortune if I hand you over to them.
找武器 你可能得杀出一条血路
Look for a weapon. You may have to shoot your way out.
我记忆中的鲍德温巴斯托
The Balduino Basto I remember would've wanted
可远远不会满足于 向曼提柯尔卑躬屈膝 撅腰瓦腚
something more than just to bend over for Manticore.
已上传百分之35
35% uploaded.
这是你女朋友给你的那个打火机吗
Is that the lighter your girlfriend gave you?
纳迪亚
Nadia?
我听说她跟你一起出现在了意大利
I heard she was with you in Italy.
她怎么了
What happened to her?
她死了
She's gone.
那你为什么还要战斗 是为了她吗
So, why do you still fight? For her?
为了她的回忆
Her memory?
上传即将完成 赶快收场吧
Upload's almost complete, start wrapping this up.
凯恩 我很惊讶 你居然会爱上一个
I'm surprised, Kane, that you, of all people would carry a torch
曾经出卖过你 并且把堡垒摧毁的女人
for the woman who sold you out. Who brought Citadel to its knees.
数据传输完成 赶快出来
Transfer's complete. Get out of there.
你到底在说什么
The hell are you talking about?
堡垒内部有曼提柯尔的人
Manticore had somebody working on the inside.
也就是你的女友 纳迪亚
It was your girl Nadia.
反正起码大家都是这么传的
Or at least, that is what the whispers say.
那个贱女人死得活该
That bitch deserved to die.
凯尔 赶快出来
Kyle, you got to go now.
不是吧
Oh, shit.
你居然被个妞儿耍了
You got played by a piece of ass.
我还以为梅森凯恩是个真男人呢
I thought Mason Kane was supposed to be a real man.
我还以为 你爸跟妓女睡的时候戴了套呢
I thought your dad wore condoms when he slept with whores.
凯尔
Kyle!
你这是急着送死
You are in a very big hurry to die.
今天不行 我要走出这里
Not today. I'm walking out of here.
把枪对准克里斯蒂亚诺
Point it at Christiano.
鲍德温根本不在乎你开枪杀了他 但如果杀了他孩子...
Balduino won't give a shit if you shot him, but his kid...
杀了他 你还在等什么
Kill him. What are you waiting for?
让他们把枪放下
Tell them to lower their guns.
你先放下
You first.
杀了他
Shoot him.
这他妈是什么情况
What the fuck's going on here?
他刚才说的是什么
What was he talking about?
纯粹胡扯 他就是个骗子
Horseshit. He's a liar.
伯纳德说过 堡垒的沦陷是内部出了叛徒
Bernard said the Citadel hit was an inside job.
有人叛变了 但他不知道那个人是谁
That someone turned but he didn't know who.
是你吗
Was it you?
你想想 凯尔
Think about it, Kyle.
如果我在跟曼提柯尔合作
If I was working with Manticore,
那我为什么要闯入暗点 营救堡垒的特工呢
why would I be trying to break into a black site to free a Citadel agent,
而且我为什么要救你命呢
and why the fuck are you still alive?
他跟我聊起你的时候 你一个劲儿地让我出来
You tried to pull me out when he started talking about you...
那是因为我不想让你送死
Because I didn't want you to get killed.
你为什么不告诉我 你跟梅森曾经是一对儿
And why not just tell me you and Mason were a thing?
因为梅森和我之间的事情 只是他跟我之间的事情
Because what happened between me and Mason is between me and Mason.
你现在坐在撤离的车里
You're in a getaway car
全世界所有的曼提柯尔特工都在找你
with every Manticore agent in the world looking for you.
所以 你要么跟我合作
So, you can either do this with me
要么就滚下车
or get the fuck out.
建议你打字的时候慎重一点
I'd be very careful what I type.
这是布瑞尔 对吧
That's Brielle, right?
不会吧
No.
她还活着
She's alive.
她叫艾比
Her name is Abby.
她嫁给了梅森凯恩
And she's married to Mason Kane.
我可以带你去见她
I can take you to her.
如果你把我从这里救出去 我就把一切都告诉你
If you get me out of here, I'll tell you everything...
因为你所知道的一切都是谎言
...because everything you know is a lie.
? I was told a million times ?
? Of all the troubles in my way ?
? Mind you grow a little wiser ?
? Little better every day ?
这是我们的新一级行动员吗
This our new Tier-One?
她跟我说 我会爱你的
She told me I'm gonna love you.
你不会的
You won't.
《堡垒》下集精彩看点
要想让他们相信你的谎言
The only way they're gonna believe your lie
首先你自己要信
is if you do.
塞莱斯特已经失联三个月了
Celeste has been dark for three months.
你也知道打入内部是什么样的
You know what it's like on the inside.
她跟我能力一样强
She's just as capable as I am.
这正是我所担心的
That's what I'm worried about.
你当初就不应该让我加入
You never should have brought me on.
堡垒
字幕翻译:腐哥
创意监督 罗婷婷